const questions = [
    { id: 1, question: "What is React?", options: ["Library", "Framework", "Language"], answer: "Library" },
    { id: 2, question: "Who maintains React?", options: ["Google", "Facebook", "Microsoft"], answer: "Facebook" },
    { id: 3, question: "What is JSX?", options: ["JavaScript XML", "Java XML", "JavaScript eXtension"], answer: "JavaScript XML" },
    { id: 4, question: "What hook is used to manage state in a functional component?", options: ["useState", "useEffect", "useContext"], answer: "useState" },
    { id: 5, question: "Which of the following is a lifecycle method in React?", options: ["componentDidMount", "useState", "useReducer"], answer: "componentDidMount" },
    { id: 6, question: "What is the default port number for a React development server?", options: ["3000", "8000", "5000"], answer: "3000" },
    { id: 7, question: "How can you pass data from a parent to a child component?", options: ["Props", "State", "Context"], answer: "Props" },
    { id: 8, question: "Which hook is used to perform side effects in a functional component?", options: ["useEffect", "useReducer", "useMemo"], answer: "useEffect" },
    { id: 9, question: "What is a virtual DOM?", options: ["A copy of the real DOM", "A library", "A programming language"], answer: "A copy of the real DOM" },
    { id: 10, question: "Which method is used to update the state in a class component?", options: ["setState", "updateState", "changeState"], answer: "setState" }
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  